cricketmove.com 2013-05-29

# Privacy Policy | Live Cricket

We _**( Cricketmove.com)** ****_ never share any data or information (got for whatever cause and by whatever source or provided by your own self to us) with any other person ever, but just when need to give it under strict orders from a competent Court of Law.

We _**( Cricketmove.com)** ****_ can just get limited information about its loggers without directly asking the persons any questions. This information is collected to keep our web site optimized to the preferences of the majority of our fans with a view to treat them better.

There is information that a visitor provides when he joins the account initially, participates in polls, promotions and contests, or fills out surveys. Our privacy policy covers all such information and never shares it with others. We keep this information strictly to ourselves and use it only to serve you better. This information is not and will not ever be shared with any 3rd party.

Our privacy policy is not for that information which you write in the open public section. Naturally our privacy policy does not and cannot cover this information. It is simply impossible for us to check others using this information for their own valid or invalid purposes.

We _**( Cricketmove.com)** ****_ never give or sell email addresses of loggers to any other parties.

_**Changes to this policy**_

We _**( Cricketmove.com)** ****_ may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and we will post the latest version. If we ever wish to use your personal information in a way which is incompatible with the information in this Privacy Policy, we will only do so with your consent.

_**Queries**_

If you have queries about our use of personal information, you can write to us.
